[{"question": "np.tri(2, k = 1) + np.diag([1, 2]) = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "np.array([[2, 0], [1, 3]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[1, 2], [1, 1]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 1], [1, 3]])", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([[1, 0], [1, 3]])", "correct": false}], "tag": "numpy arrays", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "np.diag([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]], k = -1) = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([1, 5, 9])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([2, 6])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([4, 8])", "correct": true}], "tag": "numpy arrays", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "A = np.ones(shape = [2, 2])<br>A + np.array([1, 1]) = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "np.array([[2, 2], [1, 1]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 1], [2, 1]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 2], [2, 2]])", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([[1, 2], [1, 2]])", "correct": false}], "tag": "numpy arrays", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "A = np.array([[12, 15], [18, 21]])<br>B = np.array([6, 3])<br>A / B = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "np.array([[2, 5], [18, 21]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[12, 15], [3, 7]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 5], [3, 7]])", "correct": true}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "When np.transpose(A) = np.linalg.inv(A); then A is a ", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "symmetric matrix", "correct": false}, {"answer": "skew-symmetric matrix", "correct": false}, {"answer": "orthogonal matrix", "correct": true}, {"answer": "identity matrix", "correct": false}], "tag": "matrices numpy", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "A = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [3, 2, 1]])<br>B = np.array([4, 5, 6])<br>A @ B  = C<br>We can say that", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "C is a linear combination of the columns in A", "correct": true}, {"answer": "C is a linear combination of the rows in A", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The operation would give an error.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Shape of C = (1, 2)", "correct": false}], "tag": "matrices", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "A = np.array([1, 1, 1])<br>B = np.array([[1], [1], [1]])<br>(A @ B).shape = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "(1, 3)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(1)", "correct": true}, {"answer": "(3, 1)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(3, 3)", "correct": false}], "tag": "matrices", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "What would be the inverse of the matrix:<br>np.array([[3, -6], [2, -4]])", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Inverse does not exist", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, -4], [3, -6]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[-3, 6],  [-2, 4]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[6, -9],  [3, -4]])", "correct": false}], "tag": "matrices", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "The rank of a matrix determines the", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "number of linearly independent rows", "correct": false}, {"answer": "number of linearly independent columns", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": false}], "tag": "rank matrices", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}, {"question": "A = np.array([1, 2])<br>B = np.array([3, 4, 5])<br>np.hstack([A, B]) = ?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([1, 2, 3, 4, 5])", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([[1, 3, 4, 5], [2, 3, 4, 5]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[1, 2, 3], [1, 2, 4], [1, 2, 5]])", "correct": false}], "tag": "numpy matrices", "lecture_file": "15_intro_linear_algebra"}]